Robert Francis Papers
Robert Francis Papers
- Writings
  - Worksheets
    - "Magazines containing poems not included in my volumes" published material, Aug. 1953-Oct. 1967
      - "The Old Peppermint Ladies" in The New England Galaxy, vol. 3, no. 4 ( Spring, 1962), p. 43. (Box 8)
      - "A Tribute to W. H. Auden and his Vocabulary" in The New Yorker, vol. 32, no. 24, ( Aug. 4, 1956), p. 28. (Box 8)
      - "Weather" in The Lyric, vol. 35, no. 2 ( Spring, 1955) p. 53. (Box 8)
  - Writings about
    - The Poetry of Robert Francis / Max Delhomme (Universite de Bordeaux, May, 1962 ). (Box 8)
- Published material
  - Forum issues containing R. Francis's work: poetry and essays (see list in folder for titles of works
    - 1946, notes (Box 9)
    - 1947-1950, 3 folders (Box 9)
  - "Harvard Film Service," catalogue, in Official Register of Harvard University, vol. XLII, no. 2, January 15, 1945 (Box 10)
- Tape recordings
  - Untitled, 1/4" 1200' plastic (Box 9)
  - Phonodiscs
    - The Harvard Vocarium Records Robert Francis Reading his own poems, 1944; 2 discs (Package 1)
    - Fassett Recording Studio: Robert Francis Reading his poems ..., 14-15 June, 1960 (Package 1)
    - Official Register of Harvard University, vol. XLII, no. 2 Harvard Film Service...Catalogue of Phonograph Recordings..., 15 Jan. 1945 (Package 1)